onlinegamesquad.com 2017-05-19

# Privacy policy – MadDwarf.com

## Introduction

We want our users to always be aware of any information we collect, how we use it, and  
under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  

## IntroductionInformation we collect and use

We respect each site visitor’s right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use  
information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This  
statement applies solely to information collected on this website.  
For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes no  
information regarding the domain or e-mail address.  

## The information we collect is:

used to improve the content of our Web page.  
used to notify visitors about updates to our Web site.  
never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

Registration is not required to enter our site. However, subscription to certain  
services may require a user to complete a registration form.  
During registration a user must give certain contact information, but we never sell or give  
away this information. It is only gathered to contact the user about services on our site for  
which s/he has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic  
information (income level, gender, etc.), and unique identifiers (username, password,  
etc.). Giving additional information helps provide a more personalized experience on our  
site, but is not required. 

We operate online surveys, and we never sell or share our subscribers’ email addresses.  
We do show advertisement to our users,  
which is handled by [Google Adsense](http://adsense.google.com/).  
So any such concerns with our advertising, should be directed to them respectedly. 

## Furthermore:

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users  
based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).  

## Notification Of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement.  

## Conflict Resolution

We are committed to resolving disputes within 24-48 hours. If problems arise, users may contact via our contact form.  

## Contact Information

If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please  
contact us via our [contact page](http://www.maddwarf.com/contact/).
